I came here to fix your day.
Yeah,
my name is Caio.
I'm from the Brigadier's workshop.
And this chocolate ball
what do you discover?
If what you're doing works for the number of
people who transform through your transformation.
If what you do motivates anyone to do something like that,
what you do motivates people to get up and start walking.
Are you working on what you're doing?
Twenty years from now,
we haven't been doing this anymore,
it will have been worth a scene like this.
Thank you very much.
And that scissors.
So then we're going to take a picture with my box.
With your Passenger,
Pay attention.
I don't think it's easy,
go after it,
it's on,
you can do it,
It's Sai,
bro,
think outside the box and go.
There are a lot of good people.
Yeah, us.